B. ABHISHEK YADAV

MOTION GRAPHIC DESIGNER

abhishekbathulla65.wixsite.com/abhishek

PROFILE

Highly creative and multitalented Graphic Designer with extensive experience in multimedia, marketing, and print design. Exceptional collaborative and interpersonal skills; dynamic team player with well-developed written and verbal communication abilities

	abhishek bathulla 65@gmail.com
	+91 9182566335
HYE	DERABAD, OLD MALAKPET ,
TELANGANA.	

■ WORK EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER (FACULTY)

Setkey Institute of animation (2020-2021)

MOTION GRAPHIC DESIGNER

PRAKARA (2022-2023)

■ EDUCATION

SETKEY INSTITUTE OF ANIMATION.

DIPLOMA IN MULTIMEDIA (2019-2020)

SREE VENKATESWARA JUNIOR COLLEGE

(CEC)INTERMEDIATE (2015-2017)

L SREE VENKATESWARA DEGREE COLLEGE

(B.COM)COMPUTERS (2017-2019)

Adobe Photoshop

■ EXPERTISE

Adobe illustrator

Adobe After Effects

INTERESTS

P Cricket

↓ Football

↓ Travel

Photography

jogging & Gym

SKILLS

☐ Graphic Designing

RE-Creating AI

Poster designs

↓ Title Animations